<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
<data>

<!-- conceive-plus page -->
<template id="conceive-plus" name="Conceive Plus® Fertility Lubricant">

<t t-call="website.layout">
 		 <div class="page-wrapper">

			<div class="breadcrumbs">
				<ul class="items">
							<li class="home">
						                <a href="/" title="Go to Home Page">
						        Home                </a>
						            </li>
						            <span style="font-size: 10px;"> &gt;</span>
						        <li class="home">
						                <a href="/brands" title="Go to brands">
						        Brands                </a>
						            </li>
						            <span style="font-size: 10px;"> &gt;</span>
						        <li class="blog">
						                <strong>Conceive Plus® Fertility Lubricant</strong>
						            </li>
						</ul>
			</div>
<main id="maincontent" class="page-main">
<div class="columns"><div class="column main">
<br/>
<div class="entry-content">
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">
				 <div class="col-md-12">
                    <h3 class=""><strong> Conceive Plus® Fertility Lubricant </strong></h3>
                    <p><img class="" title="" src="/sasmar_theme/static/src/img/terms.jpg" alt="Terms and Conditions" width="680" height="248"/></p>
              <p><strong>CONCEIVE PLUS® IS THE ONLY FERTILITY LUBRICANT TO PRO-ACTIVELY AID YOUR CHANCES OF GETTING PREGNANT.</strong></p>

<p>
<p>Conceive Plus® fertility lubricant is a internationally patented, scientifically advanced personal lubricant formulation that contains magnesium and calcium ions, essential to prolonging sperm viability and motility. Conceive Plus®  is safe for use by all couples who are trying to get pregnant, enhancing both the enjoyment and the chances of getting pregnant naturally.</p>
<p>
Regular lubricants kill or harm sperm, forming a barrier to sperm motility and effectively hindering the chances of sperm reaching the egg. Conceive Plus® preserves sperm motility and is scientifically formulated to allow the complete mixing of sperm. The gentle formulation of Conceive Plus® matches fertile cervical liquid and semen to create a conception-friendly environment that increases the chances of pregnancy naturally. The osmolarity and pH ranges of Conceive Plus are controlled to be within safe limits for sperm and egg.
</p>
<p>
Conceive Plus® is sold in more than 60 countries and is available from clinics, supermarkets and pharmacies over-the-counter.
</p>
</p>
                </div>
 		</div>
 	</div>
 </div>
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">
                <div class="col-md-12">
                    <hr class="tall"/>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>



</div></div></div></main>

		 </div>
 		</t>
	</template>

</data>
</odoo>
