<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
<data>

<!-- FAQ page -->
<template id="faq" name="FAQ">

<t t-call="website.layout">
 		 <div class="page-wrapper">

			<div class="breadcrumbs">
				<ul class="items">
						        <li class="home">
						                <a href="/" title="Go to Home Page">
						        Home                </a>
						            </li>
						        <span style="font-size: 10px;"> &gt;</span>
						        <li class="item blog">
						                <strong>FAQs</strong>
						            </li>
						</ul>
			</div>
<main id="maincontent" class="page-main">
<div class="columns"><div class="column main">
<br/>
<div class="entry-content">
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">

                <div class="col-md-12">

                    <h3 class=""><strong>FAQs</strong></h3>
                    <p><img class="" title="FAQs" src="/sasmar_theme/static/src/img/questions-faqs.jpg" alt="FAQs" width="680" height="248"/></p>
           <h1 dir="ltr"><em>Have a question? Here are the answers to the most asked questions....</em> </h1>
<h3 dir="ltr"><span>How much is delivery?</span></h3>
<p dir="ltr">See  <a href="/shipping-returns">Shipping &amp; Returns</a>  for delivery costs and free delivery options.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><span>How can I track my order?</span></h3>
<p dir="ltr"><span>After ordering, you will receive two emails from us. The </span><span>first email</span><span> confirms that your payment has been successful. The </span><span>second email</span><span> is your </span><span>shipping information</span><span> email. This email will contain a tracking link so you can track the status of your order.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Sometimes there is a 24-36 hour delay from the time your parcel actually begins transit to the time you get your email (that's just the time it takes our systems to process all the information!).</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>If your parcel says 'delivered' when you click the tracking link and you have not received it - you will need to go to your local Post office and present ID to collect the item/s purchased. Sometimes the "pickup reminder notice" that is left when nobody is home to sign on delivery, can go missing.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>If there is a problem with the delivery of your item, please contact the courier company for information before contacting us. You will find their details on your tracking link.</span></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">I never received a tracking email</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Ensure that you're checking the correct email address. The email address you entered to make you purchase is the email address all information will be sent to. Check your spam/junk mail too. If you cannot find your tracking email - you can log into your account to <a href="/web">view your order history</a>.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><span>How long will it take to receive my order?</span></h3>
<table style="height: 337px; width: 438px; border: 2px solid #eee;" border="0">
<tbody>
<tr align="left" valign="top">
<td>
<h5><strong>Destination</strong></h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5><strong>Express</strong></h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5><strong>Regular</strong></h5>
</td>
</tr>
<tr align="left" valign="top">
<td>
<h5>United States</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>1-2 days</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>2-5 days</h5>
</td>
</tr>
<tr align="left" valign="top">
<td>
<h5>South America</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>5-7 days</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>7-14 days</h5>
</td>
</tr>
<tr align="left" valign="top">
<td>
<h5>Central America</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>5-7 days</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>7-14 days</h5>
</td>
</tr>
<tr align="left" valign="top">
<td>
<h5>Middle East</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>5-7 days</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>7-14 days</h5>
</td>
</tr>
<tr align="left" valign="top">
<td>
<h5>Africa</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>5-7 days</h5>
</td>
<td>
<h5>4-10 days</h5>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size: x-small;"><strong><em>Your country not listed here?</em></strong> <a href="http://www.sasmar.com/">Change store region</a></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">These above delivery times are supplied by the shipping companies that we use in each location. Sometimes, the shipping time may extend beyond these expected time frames. However, your tracking link will always keep you up to date with where your parcel is in transit. <strong>Couriers delivery Monday to Friday only.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>If you wish to make a complaint about your product not reaching you within indicated time frames, please contact the postal company in charge of shipping your parcel, not us - this will be a much more efficient way of tracking down your parcel and working out why it is delayed.  Email us if you have contacted the shipping company and are still having difficulties with your order</span></p>
<h3>What payment methods do you accept?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">We accept all major credit and debit cards (Visa, MasterCard, Amex, Debit Cards) as well as Paypal. </p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Is this website secure?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Yes. This website is secured with a Geotrust Premium SSL certificate that also secures users on mobiles and handheld devices. The internet s one million most-visited domains rely on GeoTrust SSL more than any other certificate authority.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><span>Where are your products manufactured?</span></h3>
<p>Our factory is in France and all SASMAR products are produced there and then transported to our warehouses around the globe.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Where do you ship from?</h3>
<p>This store ships from our warehouses within the United States in PA and LA.</p>
<h3>I would like to know if this product has any animal sources?</h3>
<p><span>NO. SASMAR does not use any animal products in the production of its products. If the product contains glycerine, we use only 100% medical grade vegitable derived glycerine.</span></p>
<h3><span>Are your products FDA Approved to be sold in the United States?</span></h3>
<p><span>Yes, all SASMAR products offered on this website are cleared to be sold in the United States. In 2013 the FDA (Federal Drug Administration) cleared SASMAR Personal Lubricants and SASMAR Conceive Plus for premarket approval. Most personal lubricants in the USA do not have this clearance and cannot be legally sold, beware that "<em>manufactured in FDA approved facilities</em>" does not mean the product has been cleared by the FDA. A google search will confirm SASMAR products are FDA cleared.</span></p>
<h3>I have PCOS, will Conceive Plus help me?</h3>
<p><span>Conceive Plus is not a medicine and not specifically designed to treat any infertility issues such as PCOS. The product helps to create a friendly environment that assists the natural functions of the body to increase the changes of pregnancy. During the past two years we have received a number of testimonials from women with PCOS that have become pregnant and believe that Conceive Plus was certainly a contributing factor. </span></p>
<p>As the only personal lubricant with calcium and magnesium ions that are essential for the process of fertilization we recommend the product to all couples who are trying to conceive, including those with PCOS as the product is safe to use by all couples, as recommended by doctors.</p>
<h3>When should we use Conceive Plus for it to work?</h3>
<p>Conceive Plus Fertility Lubricant is for couples who are trying to get pregnant naturally. If you and your partner are trying to get pregnant, use Conceive Plus everytime your have sexual intercourse, to increase chances of getting pregnant naturally.</p>
<h3>Are SASMAR Personal Lubricants safe to use with condoms?</h3>
<p><span lang="EN-AU">Yes, SASMAR </span><span lang="EN-AU">personal lubricants are compatible with natural latex, polyisoprene and polyurethane-based condoms.</span></p>
<p><span lang="EN-AU"><span lang="EN-AU">Yes, if you are not trying to conceive Conceive Plus </span><span lang="EN-AU">personal lubricants are compatible with natural latex and polyisoprene condoms.</span></span></p>
<h3><span lang="EN-AU">Are SASMAR Personal Lubricants and Conceive Plus tested for Biocomptibility and Irritation?</span></h3>
<p><span lang="EN-AU">Yes, SASMAR </span><span lang="EN-AU">personal lubricants</span><span lang="EN-AU"> conform to the FDA s recognized standards for safety and performance of patient personal lubricants under </span><span lang="EN-AU"><span lang="EN-AU">ISO 10993-5, -10, -11 for biocompatibility. The tests include the following: <span lang="EN-AU">Vaginal Irritation, <span lang="EN-AU">Cytotoxicity, </span></span></span></span><span lang="EN-AU">Acute Systemic Toxicity, <span lang="EN-AU">Maximization Test For Delayed-Type Hypersensitivity. Results of the testing showed that the products are non-toxic, do not have a cytotoxic effect, are are non-irritating.</span></span></p>
<p><span lang="EN-AU"><span lang="EN-AU">Conceive Plus <span lang="EN-AU">conform to the FDA s recognized standards for safety and performance of patient personal lubricants under </span><span lang="EN-AU"><span lang="EN-AU">ISO 10993-5, -10, -11 for biocompatibility. Conceive Plus </span></span>has been extensively tested by independent laboritories and a published clinical study show sperm safety. Results of the testing showed that the products are non-toxic, do not have a cytotoxic effect, are are non-irritating. <strong>Conceive Plus is the ONLY personal lubricant that has been cleared by the FDA as "gamete, fertilization, and embryo compatible"</strong>.</span></span></p>
<p><span lang="EN-AU"><span lang="EN-AU">For more information on Conceive Plus, visit <a href="http://www.conceiveplus.com/" target="_blank">www.conceiveplus.com</a></span></span></p>
<h3><span lang="EN-AU"><span lang="EN-AU">Is it possible to be allergic to Conceive Plus?</span></span></h3>
<p><span>Tests conducted on Conceive Plus showed that the formula is non-irritating to vaginal tissue and does not cause any sensitization reactions or hypersensitivity. If you experience irritation, or discomfort using the product, discontinue use and if it persists consult a doctor.</span></p>
<h3><span>Do you offer refunds or product guarantees?</span></h3>
<p><span>Due to the nature of our products, and in conformity with regulations imposed by the FDA, TGA and other health agencies we do not accept product returns. Everyone' body is different, and as such we understand that our products may not be the right choice for everyone therfore we do not offer any product guarantees. Please note that Conceive Plus is a personal lubricant that is proven safe for sperm and is designed for couples who are trying to conceive, no guarantee is given on your own success while using the product. </span></p>
<h3><span>I'm trying to get pregnant, Should I use the Conceive Plus Applicator or the Tube?</span></h3>
<p><span><span>We suggest using both the applicators and multi-use tube when you are trying to get pregnant. Conceive Plus</span><span> </span><span> Pre-filled Applicators, they are really easy to use, convenient and a safe way to deposit the sperm-friendly lubricant intra-vaginally - use one about 15 minutes before intercourse to allow the lubricant to coat the vagina and curvix. Use the Multi-use tube together with your partner to provide additional moisture and increase the pleasure of baby making together.</span></span></p>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">
                <div class="col-md-12">
                    <hr class="tall"/>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>



</div></div></div></main>

		 </div>
 		</t>
	</template>

</data>
</odoo>
