<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
<data>

<!-- FAQ page -->
<template id="our-terms" name="Our Terms">

<t t-call="website.layout">
 		 <div class="page-wrapper">

			<div class="breadcrumbs">
				<ul class="items">
								<li class="home">
						                <a href="/" title="Go to Home Page">
						        Home                </a>
						            </li>
						            <span style="font-size: 10px;"> &gt;</span>
						        <li class="blog">
						                <strong>Our Terms</strong>
						            </li>
						</ul>
			</div>
<main id="maincontent" class="page-main">
<div class="columns"><div class="column main">
<br/>
<div class="entry-content">
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">
                <div class="col-md-3">


                    <div class="widget block block-categories" data-bind="scope: 'categories'">
						<div class="block-title">
							<strong style="text-transform: uppercase;">Categories</strong>
						</div>

						<ul class="accordion" id="accordion-2">
										<li><em class="fa fa-caret-right theme-color"></em><a href="#" title="About us"> Personal Lubricants</a></li>
										<li><em class="fa fa-caret-right theme-color"></em><a href="#" title="About us"> Trying for a Baby</a></li>
										<li><em class="fa fa-caret-right theme-color"></em><a href="#" title="About us"> Sensual Massage</a></li>

										</ul>

					</div>

  				<!-- Most Popular Products -->
					<t t-call="sasmar_theme.most_popular_products" />
				<!-- End Most Popular Products -->

                </div>
                <div class="col-md-9">

                    <h3 class=""><strong> OUR TERMS</strong></h3>
                    <p><img class="" title="Terms and Conditions" src="/sasmar_theme/static/src/img/terms.jpg" alt="Terms and Conditions" width="680" height="248"/></p>
              <p><strong>Disclaimers</strong></p>
<p>You acknowledge and agree that:</p>
<div>  </div>
<p>A. Although we strive to provide on this Web site the latest developments relating to our products and services, and other information about our company, we do not warrant the accuracy, effectiveness and suitability of any information contained in this Web site. Each person assumes full responsibility and all risks arising from use of this Internet site. The information is presented "AS IS" and may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. SASMAR reserves the right to make additions, deletions, or modifications to the information at any time without any prior notification.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p>B. SASMAR MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND OR NATURE WITH RESPECT TO THE INFORMATION OR CONTENT POSTED ON THIS WEB SITE. SASMAR HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, CREATED BY LAW, CONTRACT OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL SASMARBE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND OR NATURE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL (INCLUDING LOSS OF PROFIT) CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE EXISTENCE OR USE OF THIS INTERNET SITE AND/OR THE INFORMATION OR CONTENT POSTED ON THIS WEB SITE, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SASMAR HAS BEEN ADVISED AS TO THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p>C. SASMAR is not responsible, and provides no warranty whatsoever, for the accuracy, effectiveness, timeliness and suitability of any information or content obtained from third parties, including any hyperlinks to or from third-party sites. Except as otherwise provided on this Web site, SASMAR will not edit, censor or otherwise control any content provided by third parties on any bulletin board, chat room or other similar forums posted on its Web site. Such information should, therefore, be considered as suspect and is not endorsed by SASMAR.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p><strong>Your use</strong></p>
<p>You understand, acknowledge, and agree to the following:</p>
<div>  </div>
<p>A. By using this Web site, you agree not to disrupt or intercept our electronic information posted on this Web site or on any of our servers. You also agree not to attempt to circumvent any security features of our Web site, and to abide by all applicable, local, state, federal and international laws, rules and regulations.</p>
<p>B. You grant to SASMAR the right to use all content you upload or otherwise transmit to this Web site, subject to these Terms and Conditions and SASMAR  s Privacy Policy in any manner SASMAR chooses, including, but not limited, to copying, displaying, performing or publishing it in any format whatsoever, modifying it, incorporating it into other material or making a derivative work based on it.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p>C. Except as expressly stated and agreed upon in advance by SASMAR, no confidential relationship shall be established in the event that any user of this Internet site should make any oral, written or electronic communication to SASMAR(such as feedback, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, etc.). If any SASMAR Web site requires or requests that such information be provided, and that such information contains personal identifying information (e.g., name, address, phone number), SASMAR shall obtain, use and maintain it in a manner consistent with our Privacy Policy. Otherwise, such communication and any information submitted therewith shall be considered non-confidential, and SASMAR shall be free to reproduce, publish or otherwise use such information for any purposes whatsoever including, without limitation, the research, development, manufacture, use or sale of products incorporating such information. The sender of any information to SASMAR is fully responsible for its content, including its truthfulness and accuracy and its non-infringement of any other person's proprietary or privacy rights.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p><strong>Refunds and Product Returns</strong></p>
<p>Due to the personal nature of SASMAR products product returns are NOT accepted. Please choose carefully as we are not permitted to accept product returns should you change your mind after your order has been shipped. If you have any questions or need help to select the product that best suits your requirements please contact us using the contact us page on this website.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p>
<p><strong>Delays and customs clearance</strong></p>
<p>We can ship to virtually any address in the world however  SASMAR is NOT responsible for any clearance delays, custom costs, import costs for importation into countries outside of Europe, Australia, Hong Kong, United States and the United Kingdom where we do not have a warehouse. You accept full responsibility for any problems that may occur in your country and agree to hold SASMAR harmless in the event that the order is not delivered due to a customs clearance issue.</p>
<p>By accessing or using this Web site, you agree that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to these Terms and Conditions, as they may be amended from time to time, as well as to the terms of our Privacy Policy, which is hereby incorporated into these Terms and Conditions. You are responsible for periodically reviewing these Terms and Conditions for applicable changes. Your use of this Web site after posting by us of any changes to these Terms and Conditions constitutes your acceptance to those changes. If you disagree with these Terms and Conditions (as they may be amended from time to time), or are dissatisfied with this Web site, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using this site.</p>
</p>
<p><strong>Product labeling</strong></p>
<p>Unless otherwise noted, product names, descriptions and labeling are of European origin in English. Products may not be available in all countries or may be available under a different brand name, in different strengths, or for different indications. No director, employee, agent, or representative of SASMAR, its subsidiaries and affiliates are engaged in rendering medical advice, diagnosis, treatment or other medical services that in any way create a physician-patient relationship through this Web site. No patient data is available regarding viable pregnancies or birth outcomes as a result of using the Conceive Plus product.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p><strong>INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY</strong></p>
<p>The information, documents, and related graphics published in this Internet Web site (the "Information") are the sole property of SASMAR, except for information provided by third-party providers under contract to SASMAR, its subsidiaries or affiliates. Permission to use the Information is granted, provided that (1) the above copyright notice appears on all copies; (2) use of the Information is for informational and non-commercial or personal use only; (3) the Information is not modified in any way; and (4) no graphics available from this Internet site are used separate from accompanying text. SASMAR is not responsible for content provided by third-party providers, and you are prohibited from distribution of such material without permission of the owner of the copyright therein. Except as permitted above, no license or right, express or implied, is granted to any person under any patent, trademark or other proprietary right of SASMAR. No use of any SASMAR trademark, trade names, trade dress and products in this Internet site may be made without the prior written authorization of SASMAR, except to identify the product or services of the company.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p><strong>Privacy and security</strong></p>
<p>SASMAR is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We understand the importance of privacy to our customers and visitors to our Web site. Our use of personally identifiable information is governed by our Privacy Policy and by accessing and using our Web site, you agree to be bound by that policy. You recognize and agree that when submitting your personally identifiable information to SASMAR.com, while SASMAR has safeguards in place to prevent unauthorized access or interception, there is no absolute guarantee of security.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p>IN THE UNLIKELY EVENT OF AN INTERCEPTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS DESPITE OUR EFFORTS, SASMAR SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR SUCH INTERCEPTIONS OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, OR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING LOST PROFITS) SUFFERED BY A CUSTOMER OR USER, EVEN IF SASMAR HAS PREVIOUSLY BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SASMAR DOES NOT WARRANT, EITHER EXPRESSLY OR IMPLIEDLY, THAT THE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY ANY CUSTOMER SHALL BE FREE FROM INTERCEPTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, AND DOES NOT PROVIDE ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. EACH CUSTOMER IS RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF HIS OR HER OWN PASSWORD.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p><strong>Limitation of liability</strong></p>
<p>SASMAR does not assume any liability for the materials, information and opinions provided on, posted to, or otherwise available through, this Web site. Reliance on these materials, information and opinions is solely at your own risk. SASMAR disclaims any liability for injury or damages resulting from the use of this Web site, or the content contained thereon. THIS SASMAR WEB SITE, THE SITE CONTENT, AND THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PROVIDED ON OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN   AS IS   AND   AS AVAILABLE   BASIS, WITH ALL FAULTS. IN NO EVENT SHALL SASMAR, OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, VENDORS, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS (HEREINAFTER   SASMAR PARTIES  ) BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE, THIS WEB SITE, THE SITE CONTENT, ANY SERVICES PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THIS WEB SITE OR ANY LINKED SITE, INCLUDING ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY, LOST PROFITS OR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM DELAY, INTERRUPTION IN SERVICE, VIRUSES, DELETION OF FILES OR ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS, OR ERRORS, OMISSIONS OR OTHER INACCURACIES IN THIS WEB SITE OR THE SITE CONTENT, WHETHER OR NOT THERE IS NEGLIGENCE BY SASMAR AND WHETHER OR NOT SASMAR HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH DAMAGES. Some countries / states do not allow the limitation of liability, so this provision may not apply to you. PLEASE BE AWARE THAT ADDITIONAL LEGAL NOTICES, DISCLAIMERS, AND OTHER TERMS AND CONDITIONS MAY APPLY TO THIS AND OTHER WEB SITES OWNED OR OPERATED BY SASMAR, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR AFFILIATES.</p>
<p>
<p>Conceive Plus and SASMAR products are manufactured by: SASMAR SPRL.  </p>
<p><strong>This website is controlled and operated by</strong>: SASMAR Limited, 69 Old Broad Street London EC2M 1QS United Kingdom. Registered in England number 06966600 VAT GB100 1117 08</p>
<p>  </p>
</p>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">
                <div class="col-md-12">
                    <hr class="tall"/>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>



</div></div></div></main>

		 </div>
 		</t>
	</template>

</data>
</odoo>
