<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
<data>

<!-- Submit an Idea page -->
<template id="submit-an-idea" name="Submit an Idea">

<t t-call="website.layout">
 		 <div class="page-wrapper">

			<div class="breadcrumbs">
				<ul class="items">
								<li class="home">
						                <a href="/" title="Go to Home Page">
						        Home                </a>
						            </li>
						            <span style="font-size: 10px;"> &gt;</span>
						        <li class="home">
						                <a href="/innovation" title="Go to Innovation">
						        Innovation                </a>
						            </li>
						               <span style="font-size: 10px;"> &gt;</span>
						        <li class="blog">
						                <strong>Submit an Idea</strong>
						            </li>
						</ul>
			</div>
<main id="maincontent" class="page-main">
<div class="columns"><div class="column main">
<br/>
<div class="entry-content">
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">
                <!--<div class="col-md-3">


                    <div class="widget block block-categories" data-bind="scope: 'categories'">
						<div class="block-title">
							<strong style="text-transform: uppercase;">Categories</strong>
						</div>

						<ul class="accordion" id="accordion-2">
										<li><em class="fa fa-caret-right theme-color"></em><a href="#" title="About us"> Personal Lubricants</a></li>
										<li><em class="fa fa-caret-right theme-color"></em><a href="#" title="About us"> Trying for a Baby</a></li>
										<li><em class="fa fa-caret-right theme-color"></em><a href="#" title="About us"> Sensual Massage</a></li>

										</ul>

					</div>-->

  				<!-- Most Popular Products -->
					<!--<t t-call="sasmar_theme.most_popular_products" />-->
				<!-- End Most Popular Products

                </div>-->
                <div class="col-md-12">

                    <h3 class=""><strong> Submit an Idea </strong></h3>
                    <p><img class="" title="Terms and Conditions" src="/sasmar_theme/static/src/img/terms.jpg" alt="Terms and Conditions" width="680" height="248"/></p>
              <p><strong>Submit an Idea</strong></p>

<p>
<p>We can ship to virtually any address in the world however  SASMAR is NOT responsible for any clearance delays, custom costs, import costs for importation into countries outside of Europe, Australia, Hong Kong, United States and the United Kingdom where we do not have a warehouse. You accept full responsibility for any problems that may occur in your country and agree to hold SASMAR harmless in the event that the order is not delivered due to a customs clearance issue.</p>
<p>By accessing or using this Web site, you agree that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to these Terms and Conditions, as they may be amended from time to time, as well as to the terms of our Privacy Policy, which is hereby incorporated into these Terms and Conditions. You are responsible for periodically reviewing these Terms and Conditions for applicable changes. Your use of this Web site after posting by us of any changes to these Terms and Conditions constitutes your acceptance to those changes. If you disagree with these Terms and Conditions (as they may be amended from time to time), or are dissatisfied with this Web site, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using this site.</p>
</p>
<p><strong>Product labeling</strong></p>
<p>Unless otherwise noted, product names, descriptions and labeling are of European origin in English. Products may not be available in all countries or may be available under a different brand name, in different strengths, or for different indications. No director, employee, agent, or representative of SASMAR, its subsidiaries and affiliates are engaged in rendering medical advice, diagnosis, treatment or other medical services that in any way create a physician-patient relationship through this Web site. No patient data is available regarding viable pregnancies or birth outcomes as a result of using the Conceive Plus product.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p><strong>INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY</strong></p>
<p>The information, documents, and related graphics published in this Internet Web site (the "Information") are the sole property of SASMAR, except for information provided by third-party providers under contract to SASMAR, its subsidiaries or affiliates. Permission to use the Information is granted, provided that (1) the above copyright notice appears on all copies; (2) use of the Information is for informational and non-commercial or personal use only; (3) the Information is not modified in any way; and (4) no graphics available from this Internet site are used separate from accompanying text. SASMAR is not responsible for content provided by third-party providers, and you are prohibited from distribution of such material without permission of the owner of the copyright therein. Except as permitted above, no license or right, express or implied, is granted to any person under any patent, trademark or other proprietary right of SASMAR. No use of any SASMAR trademark, trade names, trade dress and products in this Internet site may be made without the prior written authorization of SASMAR, except to identify the product or services of the company.</p>
<div>  </div>
<p><strong>Privacy and security</strong></p>
<p>SASMAR is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We understand the importance of privacy to our customers and visitors to our Web site. Our use of personally identifiable information is governed by our Privacy Policy and by accessing and using our Web site, you agree to be bound by that policy. You recognize and agree that when submitting your personally identifiable information to SASMAR.com, while SASMAR has safeguards in place to prevent unauthorized access or interception, there is no absolute guarantee of security.</p>
<div>  </div>

<p>
<p>Conceive Plus and SASMAR products are manufactured by: SASMAR SPRL.  </p>
<p><strong>This website is controlled and operated by</strong>: SASMAR Limited, 69 Old Broad Street London EC2M 1QS United Kingdom. Registered in England number 06966600 VAT GB100 1117 08</p>
<p>  </p>
</p>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div class="row">
        <div class="row-wrapper container">
            <div class="row">
                <div class="col-md-12">
                    <hr class="tall"/>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>



</div></div></div></main>

		 </div>
 		</t>
	</template>

</data>
</odoo>
